(Leonard:)Why? Because I got an ugly,
itchy sweater,
(Leonard:)and my brother got a car?
No, I was her favourite.
Yeah, I seem to be
a few tickets short.
(Sheldon:)Are there more in the box?
(Leonard:)I think I got them all.
(Leonard:)Nope, they're not in there.
(Sheldon:)Well, you barely looked. Let me see.
No, no, no, I looked, and...
No more tickets.
(Sheldon:)-Leonard, let me look in the box.
-Okay, Okay!
(Leonard:)I'm gonna show you what's in the box.
but just... promise not to flip out?
Why would I flip out? ls it a spider?
It's a spider!
(Penny:)No, if it was a spider,
Lenny would've flipped out.
(Leonard:)Okay, Sheldon, I know I was supposed
to return this DVD a long time ago,
(Leonard:)and I know we
rented it on your card.
But ifs been, like, seven years,
(Leonard:)and clearly nothing bad has happened.
So instead of being a giant
pain in the ass, like you always are,
what if this onetime
you just tried staying calm?
(Sheldon:)That seems like a reasonable request.
Although so did, "Hoy, Leonard,
would you mind returning that DVD?"
I'm sorry. I'll take care of it.
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Leonard:)I mean it. I'm going to.
(Sheldon:)I believe you.
(Leonard:)And you're going to stay calm?
(Sheldon:)I said I would.
(Leonard:)How about that?
(Leonard:)Sheldon's being reasonable.
(Penny:)Yeah, it's freaking me out.
I'm gonna go.